You have to climb Mount Kusama
올라가야 해 쿠사마 산
and you must do a ritual.
그리고 당신은 의식을 행해야 합니다.
- But you need a date. - For your dad?
- 하지만 데이트가 필요해요. - 아버지를 위해서요?
Does your mom know about that?
너희 엄마도 그 사실을 알고 계시니?
Not for my dad! A date for you!
아빠를 위해서가 아니에요! 당신을 위한 데이트!
Look! I don't need your help!
보세요! 네 도움은 필요 없어!
You are the most useless family member!
당신은 가장 쓸모없는 사람입니다 가족이군요!
Is there... a private tour available?
있나요... 개인 여행이 가능한가요?
- Sir Justin's does that. - He said Sir Justin.
- 저스틴 경이 그런 일을 합니다. - 저스틴 경이라고 하더군요.
- Miss Cheska. - Oh?
- 미스 체스카. - 아?
- She'll come with you, too. - You're coming too, right?
- 그녀도 당신과 함께 갈 거예요. - 너도 오는 거 맞지?
- Oh, I'd love to. - Welcome to Hotel 88.
- 아, 그러고 싶습니다. - 호텔 88에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
The hotel that will force you to participate.
호텔은 참여를 강요합니다.
You said you saw a folder when Uncle Mike left.
당신은 봤다고 했어요 마이크 삼촌이 떠났을 때 폴더.
Ah, yes. I just mentioned it to Sir Henry recently.
아, 그렇죠. 방금 언급했는데 최근 헨리 경에게 전해졌습니다.
But do you know what's in it? Or who's it from?
그런데 그 안에 무엇이 들어 있는지 아시나요? 아니면 누구에게서 온 겁니까?
The courier just gave it, but I'm sure it's Sir Mike's.
택배기사가 방금 줬는데, 하지만 나는 그것이 Mike 경의 것이라고 확신합니다.
- [SCREAMS] Ahh! - What happened?
- [비명] 아! - 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
- What's that smell? - That odor needs
- 무슨 냄새야? - 그 냄새에는
to be eliminated by tonight.
제거될 예정 오늘 밤까지.
- Fine, I'll do it. - [CLATTERS]
- 알았어, 내가 할게. - [덜덜덜]
[SCREAMS] Ah!
[비명] 아!
Gio?
지오?
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[암울한 음악 재생]
Here's the mouse.
여기 마우스가 있습니다.
Do you really have to show it to me?
정말로 가지고 있나요? 나한테 보여주려고?
I didn't know you were there.
나는 몰랐다 당신은 거기에 있었습니다.
Wait! Where will you throw it?
기다리다! 어디에 던질 건가요?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[테마 음악 재생]
Gio, where will you throw it?
지오, 어디에 던질 거야?
No!
아니요!
What do you mean by "No"?
당신은 무엇을 합니까? "아니요"라는 뜻인가요?
They won't collect trash yet. It'll stink there.
아직은 쓰레기를 수집하지 않습니다. 거기 냄새가 날 거에요.
[CLICKS TONGUE] Tsk.
[혀를 클릭] 쯧쯧.
I told you not to throw it there.
내가 말했잖아 거기에 던지지 말라고.
Throw it outside the hotel premises.
밖에 던져 호텔 부지.
You're still acting bossy over this?
아직도 권위적인 척 하는구나 이것 때문에?
I think you forgot that I'm still the GM here, Gio.
내 생각엔 당신이 내가 있다는 걸 잊어버린 것 같아요 아직 GM이에요, Gio.
You're still supervising me throwing the mouse?
당신은 아직도 나를 감독하고 있어요 마우스를 던진다?
- The mouse might escape! - What?
- 쥐가 탈출할 수도 있어요! - 무엇?
What do you mean? The mouse is dead!
무슨 뜻이에요? 쥐가 죽었어!
What's going on with you?
무슨 일이야?
Whatever, just throw it far away for the hotel's safety.
뭐든 그냥 멀리 던져버려 호텔의 안전을 위해.
- No! - [CLICKS TONGUE] Tsk.
- 아니요! - [혀를 클릭] 쯧쯧.
You've always had that reaction about mice.
당신은 항상 그랬어요 쥐에 대한 그 반응.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[우울한 음악 재생]
- [LUNA] Gio, there's a mouse! - A  mouse?!
- [루나] 지오, 쥐가 있어요! - 쥐?!
- Get it! Get it! - [MOUSE SQUEAKS]
- 가져와! 그것을 얻으십시오! - [마우스 삐걱거림]
It's right there! It's right there! Get it!
바로 거기 있어요! 바로 거기 있어요! 가져와!
Hurry! Hurry!
서둘러요! 서둘러!
Go slowly, slowly!
천천히, 천천히 가세요!
[SCREAMS] Gio! It ran away!
[비명] 지오! 도망갔어!
It ran... oh no, it got away! It's under the bed!
달렸어요... 아뇨, 도망쳤어요! 침대 밑에 있어요!
- Where? - It's under the bed!
- 어디요? - 침대 밑에 있어요!
Wait, wait. You need to watch out for it.
잠깐, 잠깐만요. 조심해야 해요.
- [MOUSE SQUEAKS] - [SCREAMS] Ah!
- [마우스 삐걱거림] - [비명] 아!
There you go! Did you catch it?
여기요! 잡았나요?
- Did you catch it? - Should I take a look?
- 잡았나요? - 한번 살펴볼까요?
- Don't look! - How will I know?
- 보지 마세요! - 어떻게 알 수 있나요?
It might escape! You should knock.
탈출할 수도 있어요! 노크하셔야 해요.
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[마우스 끽끽거리는 소리]
Slowly.
천천히.
[KNOCKS]
[노크]
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[마우스 끽끽거리는 소리]
- [KNOCKS] - Hmm?
- [노크] - 흠?
I think it's not moving anymore.
더 이상 움직이지 않는 것 같아요.
Maybe it's just there.
아마도 거기에 있을 수도 있습니다.
- I think that's fine. - Sure.
- 괜찮은 것 같아요. - 물론이죠.
[PANTING]
[ 헐떡거림 ]
I'm tired.
피곤해요.
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[마우스 끽끽거리는 소리]
[SCREAMS] Ah!
[비명] 아!
What's going on?! You're so noisy!
무슨 일이야?! 너 너무 시끄러워!
What's wrong with you both?!
너희 둘 다 무슨 문제야?!
Grandma...
할머니...
[LAUGHS]
[웃음]
If this dead mouse comes back...
만약 이 죽은 쥐가 돌아왔다...
[PLASTIC RUSTLING]
[플라스틱 바스락거림]
Hmm.
흠.
You know, sometimes I think about
아시다시피, 가끔은
what I would do without you.
당신 없이 내가 무엇을 할 것인지.
Who'll chase away the mice in my life?
누가 쫓아갈까 내 인생의 쥐는?
[SCOFFS] Don't think about that.
[비웃는 소리] 그것에 대해 생각하지 마십시오.
How could I not think about that?
어떻게 안 되겠어? 생각해 보세요
They keep popping out of nowhere!
계속 터져요 갑자기!
Because that won't happen.
그런 일은 일어나지 않을 테니까.
Gio.
지오.
There are so many mice in Manila.
쥐가 너무 많아요 마닐라에서.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[우울한 음악 재생]
That won't happen because I won't leave you.
그런 일은 없을 거야 난 당신을 떠나지 않을 테니까요.
["TADHANA" BY SOFRONIO VASQUEZ PLAYING]
["타다나" BY 소프로니오 바스케스 연주 중]
["TADHANA" BY SOFRONIO VASQUEZ CONTINUES]
[소프로니오의 "타다나" 바스케스 계속]
[PLASTIC RUSTLING]
[플라스틱 바스락거림]
[CHESKA] Hey, stop frowning.
[CHESKA] 야, 찡그린 표정 좀 그만해.
There's a guest coming.
손님이 오시네요.
We'll just accompany them, right?
우리는 그냥 동행하겠습니다 그래요?
My god... Justin please...
맙소사... 저스틴 제발...
Keep in mind that you're still one of the owners.
아직이라는 걸 명심하세요 소유자 중 한 명.
Trixie and I are just siblings of the owners.
트릭시와 나는 단지 주인의 형제자매일 뿐입니다.
Stop acting like that.
그런 식으로 행동하지 마세요.
I'm doing this so I won't embarass Martin.
내가 이러는 거니까 안 그럴게. 마틴을 당황하게 하다.
My God!
맙소사!
Let's just think of it as us helping our siblings.
그냥 그렇다고 생각해보자 우리는 형제자매를 돕습니다.
- Hey! Energy! Energy! - Ah!
- 여기요! 에너지! 에너지! - 아!
There's a guest!
손님이 있어요!
How will we attract guests?
어떻게 손님을 유치할 것인가?
Stand up! Jump around! That's it! Smile!
일어서세요! 뛰어다녀라! 그게 다야! 웃다!
[CHESKA] Energy!
[체스카] 에너지!
What's up with your faces? That's not exactly welcoming.
얼굴은 어때요? 그다지 환영받는 수준은 아닙니다.
- Pull yourselves together. - Let's go?
- 함께 힘을 모으세요. - 갑시다?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[감미로운 음악 재생]
You're just wearing that?
그거만 입고 있는 거야?
Umm... for island hopping?
음... 섬 호핑을 위해?
Who said we'll go island hopping?
누가 우리가 간다고 했어? 섬 호핑?
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[감미로운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Are we not?
우리는 그렇지 않습니까?
- [JADE] Kiko. - Oh.
- [제이드] 키코. - 오.
Have you been waiting long?
오래 기다리셨나요?
Ah, not really.
아, 그렇지 않아요.
Are you ready?
준비됐나요?
Oh, our amulet!
아, 우리 부적!
We need to wear it, hurry.
우리 그거 입어야 해, 서둘러.
You did a good job with today's presentation, bud.
당신은 좋은 일을 했어요 오늘 발표는 여기까지야, 친구.
Well, of course, I got it from you dad.
물론이죠. 아빠한테서 받았어요
[ANDY] Let's get going.
[앤디] 가자.
[ANDY] What's going on?
[앤디] 무슨 일이야?
Is that Jade?
그거 제이드야?
[ANDY] Jade?
[앤디] 제이드?
Is that why you can't date her? She has a boyfriend?
그래서 그 사람이랑 사귈 수 없는 거야? 그 사람 남자친구 있어요?
[CHUCKLES]
[웃음]
- Let's go. - Mm-hmm.
- 갑시다. - 음-흠.
Wait, how do we get there?
잠깐만요, 거기 어떻게 가요?
Tricycle.
세발자전거.
- Tricycle? - Yeah. Let's go.
- 세발자전거요? - 응. 갑시다.
Okay, okay. Let's go.
알았어, 알았어. 갑시다.
Where are they going?
그들은 어디로 가는 걸까요?
[ANDY] Don't tell me you'll follow them?
[앤디] 말하지 마 당신은 그들을 따라갈 건가요?
- Dad, c'mon. Let's go. - What are you doing?
- 아빠, 어서요. 갑시다. - 뭐하세요?
C'mon, just get in.
자, 그냥 들어가세요.
- Grandpa! - Oh?
- 할아버지! - 오?
I also left your food inside the fridge.
나도 네 음식을 두고 왔어 냉장고 안에.
Don't forget to take your medicine too.
잊지 말고 받아가세요 당신의 약도요.
[BOTONG] What magazine?
[보통] 무슨 잡지요?
I'm not reading a magazine.
나는 잡지를 읽지 않습니다.
I said medicine, Grandpa. The one you need to take.
약이라고 했어요, 할아버지. 당신이 가져 가야 할 것.
Ah...
아...
Remember what I also told you, okay?
무엇을 기억하세요 나도 말했잖아, 알았지?
[BOTONG] Yes.
[보통] 네.
Do you even remember what I told you?
기억나시나요? 내가 뭐라고 말했지?
[BOTONG] Yeah, I know. I need to take my medicine.
[보통] 네, 알겠습니다. 약을 먹어야 해요.
Not that! The ritual.
그렇지 않아요! 의식.
[BOTONG] What ritual?
[보통] 무슨 의식이지?
The ritual that will prevent Sir Martin's date from happening
이를 방지하는 의식 마틴 경의 데이트 날짜는
with whoever that woman is.
그 여자가 누구든지.
My goodness.
이럴 수가.
Okay, fine.
알았어, 알았어.
- Promise, Grandpa? - Yes.
- 약속해요, 할아버지? - 예.
Oh!
오!
What is it this time?
이번에는 무엇입니까?
What?
무엇?
[AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
[주변 음악 재생]
Oh?
오?
Is there a ritual that...
그런 의식이...
will make me Sir Martin's date?
마틴 선생님과 데이트하게 될까요?
Take this, so you can have my DNA.
이것을 가져가세요. 내 DNA를 가지고 있어요.
Oh my goodness.
아, 맙소사.
- Grandpa, please. - Mhm.
- 할아버지, 부탁해요. - 음.
[BOTONG GRUMBLES]
[보통 투덜거림]
[SARI] Please.
[사리] 부탁해요.
Okay, fine.
알았어, 알았어.
- Thanks, Grandpa. - All right.
- 고마워요, 할아버지. - 괜찮은.
[SARI] Ah!
[사리] 아!
What is it this time?
이번에는 무엇입니까?
Buh-bye, Grandpa! I love you so much.
안녕히 계세요, 할아버지! 너무 사랑해요.
- Muah!
- 무아!
Bye, Grandpa! Don't forget to take your medicine, okay?
안녕, 할아버지! 잊지 마세요 약 먹으러, 알았지?
- Yes. Bye-bye! - Don't forget it! Buh-bye!
- 예. 안녕! - 잊지 마세요! 안녕!
- Bye, Grandpa! - Bye-bye!
- 안녕, 할아버지! - 안녕!
[AMBIENT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[주변 음악이 계속됨]
Do you want to come here?
여기로 오고 싶나요?
I can fetch you from there. Then you can stay here for now.
거기에서 당신을 데려올 수 있어요. 그러면 지금은 여기에 머물 수 있습니다.
Oh, don't bother!
아, 귀찮게 하지 마세요!
I'll just distract you from your work.
난 그냥 당신의주의를 산만하게 할 것입니다 당신의 직장에서.
I'm already happy...
벌써 행복해요...
with you giving me a call.
나한테 전화하는 거랑 같이.
Okay then.
그럼요.
But don't buy groceries for now, okay?
하지만 식료품은 사지 마세요. 지금은, 알았지?
Let's just get whatever you need delivered there
그냥 뭐든지 얻자 거기로 배달이 필요해
so you won't get too tired.
그러면 너무 피곤하지 않을 것입니다.
Look at this boy.
이 소년을보세요.
You wanted me to go on vacation there earlier,
내가 가길 바랐잖아 좀 더 일찍 그곳에서 휴가를 보내고 있었어
but you're not letting me out now
하지만 당신은 나를 허락하지 않습니다 지금 나가
because you don't want me to go to the wet market.
당신은 나를 원하지 않기 때문에 재래시장에 가려고.
What do you want me to do here?
내가 여기서 무엇을 하기를 바라나요?
Luna? Is that Luna?
루나? 그거 루나야?
- Luna! Luna! - Grandma, stop.
- 루나! 루나! - 할머니, 그만하세요.
- Luna, is that you? - Grandma, stop!
- 루나, 너야? - 할머니, 그만하세요!
Grandma, don't call her.
할머니, 전화하지 마세요.
[GIO'S GRANDMA] She looks so beautiful! Is that you, Luna?
[GIO'S GRANDMA] 그녀는 보인다 정말 아름다워요! 당신인가요, 루나?
Hello, Grandma.
안녕하세요, 할머니.
Yes, this is Luna.
네, 루나입니다.
[GIO'S GRANDMA] Oh, Luna! You're still beautiful and sexy.
[지오의 할머니] 아, 루나! 당신은 여전히 ​​아름답고 섹시해요.
How are you doing?
잘 지내세요?
I'm doing okay.
나는 잘 지내고 있어요.
How about you? How's your blood pressure?
당신은 어떤가요? 혈압은 어때요?
[GIO'S GRANDMA] Well, it's still high.
[지오의 할머니] 음, 여전히 높은데요.
But you know, whenever I see someone pretty, it goes down.
하지만 알다시피, 볼 때마다 누군가 예쁜 사람이 내려갑니다.
Oh my!
이런!
You haven't changed. You still joke a lot.
당신은 변하지 않았습니다. 아직도 농담을 많이 하시네요.
Take care of your health, okay?
건강 조심하세요, 알았죠?
Getting sick nowadays is really hard.
요즘 아프다 정말 어렵다.
[GIO'S GRANDMA] Thank you, dear.
[지오할머니] 고마워요 얘야.
There's a lot of you who always remind me about it.
당신 중에는 항상 나에게 상기시켜줘.
Is laing still your favorite?
레이를 아직도 좋아하시나요?
Your laing is my only favorite.
당신의 거짓말은 내가 제일 좋아하는 것.
[GIO'S GRANDMA SQUEALS] Okay then.
[지오의 할머니가 비명을 지른다] 그럼요.
I'll have some sent to you there.
좀 보내드릴게요 거기 당신에게.
Remind Gio that I'll send you some, okay?
지오에게 다음 사실을 상기시켜주세요 내가 좀 보내줄게, 알았지?
Okay then, Grandma.
그럼요, 할머니.
I'll get going to take care of some stuff.
내가 돌보러 갈게 어떤 것의.
Oh?
오?
Do you work in the hotel as well?
당신은 일합니까? 호텔에서도요?
Yes.
예.
Okay then.
그럼요.
Bye-bye, Grandma. Take care.
안녕히 계세요, 할머니. 잘 지내세요.
- Bye-bye, Grandma. - You too, dear.
- 안녕히 계세요, 할머니. - 너도 마찬가지야.
Always take care, okay?
항상 조심하세요, 알았죠?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
Hey!
안녕!
You're so naughty.
당신은 정말 버릇없어요.
You didn't even tell me that Luna was there.
나한테도 말하지 않았잖아 루나가 거기 있었다고.
It doesn't matter, Grandma.
상관없어요, 할머니.
How could it not?
어떻게 그럴 수 있지?
She's the only woman you brought to our house.
그녀는 유일한 여자입니다 당신이 우리 집에 데려왔어요.
I miss you, Grandma!
보고 싶어요, 할머니!
I miss you so much!
너무 보고 싶어요!
Hmm! There you go again!
흠! 또 가세요!
There you go again!
또 가세요!
But when you're ready, tell me the story, okay?
하지만 준비가 되면, 이야기를 들려줘, 알았지?
I love you, my grandson. I miss you too!
사랑해요, 손자님. 나도 보고 싶어!
Muah!
무아!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
[SARI] I'm sorry, sir!
[사리] 죄송해요 선생님!
You know there is a lot to do at the hotel.
당신은 많은 것이 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다 호텔에서 할 일.
The meeting with Gerard's dad is already tomorrow.
제라드의 아버지와의 만남 벌써 내일이에요.
- Then you're late?! - I'll just extend, sir!
- 그럼 늦었어?! - 그냥 연장할게요!
I'll work overtime for free!
나는 무료로 초과근무를 할 것이다!
- Wait, about Gerard's dad-- - [SHUSHES]
- 잠깐, 제라드의 아버지 얘기는-- - [쉿]
Quiet.
조용한.
Why are you shushing me?
왜 나를 조용히 시키는 거야?
Because this is a personal meeting.
이건 개인적인 일이니까 회의.
Sari, promise me you won't tell anyone else.
사리야 약속해 다른 사람한테는 말하지 않을 거예요.
[MARTIN SIGHS DEEPLY]
[마틴이 깊은 한숨을 쉬다]
Does that mean you have a date already?
그게 무슨 뜻인가요? 벌써 데이트 있어?
You don't have to worry about that.
그럴 필요는 없습니다. 그것에 대해 걱정하십시오.
I need the venue. I need food.
장소가 필요해요. 음식이 필요해요.
- And I need flowers. - You know, sir, you're right!
- 그리고 꽃도 필요해요. - 선생님, 당신 말이 맞아요!
[SHUSHES]
[쉿]
You don't have to worry about the date.
걱정하지 않아도 돼요 날짜에 대해서.
You can prove to Mr. Ronald that
당신은 로널드 씨에게 다음을 증명할 수 있습니다
you're a good businessman even if you don't have a date.
당신은 심지어 좋은 사업가예요 데이트가 없다면.
If he finds out that you're the perfect example
그 사람이 당신이라는 걸 알게 된다면 완벽한 예
of a businessman who's TDH!
TDH인 사업가의 모습입니다!
Don't tell me it's tall--
키가 크다고 말하지 마세요--
T, for thoughtful.
T, 사려 깊습니다.
You always pay attention to details and people, sir.
항상 주의를 기울이시네요 세부 사항과 사람에게.
And D, for driven.
그리고 D는 구동형을 의미합니다.
You will attack when needed to, sir!
당신은 다음과 같은 때 공격할 것이다. 꼭 필요해요!
And H, for hands-on.
그리고 H는 실습용입니다.
You're always present and involved.
당신은 항상 존재합니다 그리고 참여했습니다.
- That's you, sir! TDH! - [MARTIN] Raphie!
- 바로 당신이에요! TDH! - [마틴] 라피!
Sir! Sir! Sir!
선생님! 선생님! 선생님!
Edward, are you serious?
에드워드, 진심이에요?
We even left the car far away.
우리도 떠났어 차가 멀리 있어요.
Dad, they can't see us.
아빠, 저 사람들은 우리를 볼 수 없어요.
- Hide a bit more. - [SCOFFS]
- 좀 더 숨겨보세요. - [비웃음]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[재미있는 음악 재생]
Remind me again, why are we doing this?
다시 한번 상기시켜주세요. 우리가 왜 이러는 걸까요?
I'm not even prepared!
난 아직 준비도 안 됐어!
Look, I'm wearing leather shoes.
보세요, 저는 가죽 신발을 신고 있어요.
I'm sorry, Dad, okay?
죄송해요, 아빠, 알았죠?
After the breakfast tomorrow, we will climb the mountain.
내일 아침 식사 후, 우리는 산에 오를 것이다.
The hut you'll sleep in has been prepared already.
당신이 잠잘 오두막 이미 준비되었습니다.
You'll be fine sleeping next to each other, right?
잠은 괜찮을 거야 서로 옆에 있지, 그렇지?
You're a couple anyway.
어쨌든 당신은 커플입니다.
[EXCLAIMS]
[외침]
This guy? My boyfriend?
이놈? 내 남자친구요?
H-he's not.
하-그 사람은 아니에요.
[CHUCKLES]
[웃음]
Oh no, I'm sorry.
아뇨, 죄송합니다.
I thought you were a couple.
커플인줄 알았는데
What a waste. You look good together.
정말 낭비입니다. 당신은 함께 좋아 보인다.
Ah, her?
아, 그 사람?
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY] She's just my friend.
[긴장해서 낄낄거린다] 그녀는 단지 내 친구입니다.
Just so you know,
참고로,
we've been friends since we were kids.
우리는 친구였어 우리는 어렸을 때부터.
Oh, how adorable.
아, 정말 사랑스럽다.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[생각에 잠긴 음악 재생]
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
[바스락거리는 나뭇잎]
[EDWARD] Dad, hide!
[에드워드] 아빠, 숨어요!
Dad!
아빠!
[LAUGHS]
[웃음]
Dad, they might hear us. Be quiet!
아빠, 그들이 우리 말을 들을 수도 있어요. 조용히 하세요!
I can't help it, it's funny.
어쩔 수 없군요. 재밌네요.
Jade.
옥.
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
Jade.
옥.
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
Huh?
뭐?
[STUTTERING] Oh, it's nothing.
[말더듬] 아, 아무것도 아니에요.
I just thought I had seen...
방금 본 줄 알았는데...
Who?
WHO?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Never mind.
괜찮아요.
Don't worry about it.
걱정하지 마세요.
Okay, we'll go to the hut then.
좋아, 그럼 오두막으로 가자.
- It's this way. - Ah, let's get going.
- 이쪽이에요. - 아, 가자.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
[EDWARD] You know what, Dad?
[에드워드] 그거 알아요, 아빠?
Leave this to me.
이건 나에게 맡겨주세요.
I'll handle it myself, so just go home.
내가 직접 처리할게, 그러니 그냥 집에 가세요.
[ANDY] Why should I go home?
[앤디] 왜 집에 가야 하나요?
You brought me here then you'd tell me to go home?
그때 당신이 나를 여기로 데려왔죠 나한테 집에 가라고 말했을 거야?
No, no, no. I'm staying right here.
아니, 아니, 아니. 나는 바로 여기에 머물고 있습니다.
I want to see why you're acting like that.
이유를 알고 싶습니다. 당신은 그렇게 행동하고 있습니다.
And besides, this is free entertainment.
게다가, 이것은 무료 엔터테인먼트입니다.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
[MARTIN SIGHS] Finally!
[마틴 한숨] 드디어!
Pearl said yes?
Pearl이 그렇다고 했죠?
Yes, I'm not that close with Pearl.
응, 난 아니야 Pearl과 가깝습니다.
But as soon as I mentioned your name,
그런데 제가 언급하자마자 당신의 이름,
she immediately said yes.
그녀는 즉시 그렇다고 말했습니다.
[EXHALES DEEPLY] You're such a lifesaver, Trixie.
[깊게 숨을 내쉬다] 당신은 정말 생명의 은인이에요, 트릭시.
Do you know that?
그거 아시나요?
Thank you, Trixie.
고마워요, 트릭시.
[TRIXIE] But she said she had no dress to wear.
[트릭시] 그런데 그녀가 말했지 그녀는 입을 옷이 없었습니다.
You know, because it's last minute.
아시다시피, 마지막 순간이니까.
So, I put in your car
그래서 내가 당신 차에 태워줬어요
the dress that I was going to lend to her.
내가 갈 드레스 그녀에게 빌려주기 위해.
I had to do that because, of course,
그렇게 해야 했기 때문에, 물론이죠,
I don't know how long I'll be staying here.
얼마나 오래 걸릴지 모르겠어요 나는 여기에 머물 것이다.
[MARTIN SIGHS] I don't know what I'd do without you.
[마틴 한숨] 모르겠어요 당신 없이 내가 무엇을 할 것인지.
You even accompanied a guest on a tour, didn't you?
손님까지 동행하셨군요 여행 중이었어, 그렇지?
I'm doing this for you, brother.
난 당신을 위해 이 일을 하고 있어요, 형제님.
[MARTIN] I'll make it up to you, okay?
[마틴] 난 해낼 거야 너한테 달렸어, 알았지?
All right. Thanks. Bye. Love you.
괜찮은. 감사해요. 안녕. 사랑해요.
- Take care. - Love you.
- 조심하세요. - 사랑해요.
Buh-bye.
안녕.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[전화 신호음]
Hey!
여기요!
You won't wait for me, really?
정말 나를 기다리지 않을 건가요?
[MARTIN] This is Pearl's number.
[마틴] 이것은 펄의 번호입니다.
Call her and ask what time she needs to be picked up.
그 사람한테 전화해서 몇시냐고 물어봐 그녀는 데리러 가야 해.
Okay.
좋아요.
[PHONE CLICKS]
[전화 클릭]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[생각에 잠긴 음악 재생]
Pearl Lim.
펄림.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[혀를 클릭]
Huh?
뭐?
She looks like she's just ahead of me
그녀는 다음과 같습니다 그 사람이 나 바로 앞에 있어
because she's better in English.
왜냐면 그 사람이 영어를 더 잘하거든요.
But we're just equal in looks!
하지만 우리는 외모가 똑같습니다!
[TRIXIE] Hey!
[트릭시] 이봐!
Wait for me!
나를 기다려라!
[COUGHS]
[기침]
Hey, wait for me!
이봐, 나를 기다려!
Francheska.
프란체스카.
Go wait for her.
가서 그녀를 기다리세요.
Let's go ahead, Maria.
계속하자, 마리아.
[TRIXIE PANTING]
[트릭시 헐떡임]
Hey.
여기요.
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
Are you in bad terms?
당신은 나쁜 관계에 있습니까?
[TRIXIE SCOFFS]
[트릭시 비웃음]
Look at this woman. I was talking to you.
이 여자를 보세요. 나는 당신과 이야기하고있었습니다.
I'll bang your heads to each other, you'll see.
네 머리를 세게 쳐줄게 서로 보면 알 겁니다.
[BROODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[음울한 음악 재생]
Okay.
좋아요.
This way.
이쪽으로.
[JUSTIN SIGHS]
[저스틴 한숨]
How moody. We should just be enjoying this.
얼마나 변덕스러운지. 우리는 이것을 즐겨야 합니다.
Do you even know where we're going?
당신도 알고 있나요 우리 어디로 가는 거야?
[TRIXIE] Nope.
[트릭시] 아니요.
Then why are you all leading the way?
그럼 다들 왜 그래? 앞장서서?
You know, we should put more of this...
알잖아, 우리는 그래야 해 이것 좀 더 넣어줘...
[MAN] It's beautiful here.
[MAN] 여기는 아름다워요.
around the hotel.
호텔 주변.
Solenn?
솔렌?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYS]
[생각에 잠긴 음악 재생]
Solenn.
솔렌.
- Solenn! - Cha-Chase?
- 솔렌! - 체이스요?
Oh my god!
맙소사!
[CHUCKLES] Wow!
[웃음] 와!
I missed you!
보고 싶었어요!
I can't believe it.
믿을 수가 없어요.
We haven't seen each other in a long time.
우리는 본 적이 없다 오랜만에 서로.
How have you been?
잘 지내셨나요?
It's been what?
뭐였지?
It's been a few years, right?
몇 년이 지났죠?
[LUNA] What are you doing here?
[루나] 여기서 뭐해요?
[CHASE] Well...
[체이스] 음...
You haven't come back in Manila for a long time.
당신은 돌아오지 않았어요 오랫동안 마닐라에서
Wait a second, when did you last come to the bar?
잠깐만요 언제 그랬어요? 마지막으로 바에 왔어?
It's been a while.
오랜만이에요.
How long has it been?
얼마나 됐나요?
Wow, you know what?
와, 그거 알아요?
I used to always ask Peter where you were.
나는 항상 피터에게 물어보곤 했어요 당신이 어디에 있었는지.
You didn't even reply to me.
당신은 나에게 답장도 하지 않았습니다.
All the while, you were just here.
그동안, 당신은 방금 여기에 있었습니다.
You know, Peter and I still hang out to this day.
있잖아, Peter와 나는 아직도 오늘까지 놀아 라.
There's this new bar in QC.
QC에 새로운 바가 생겼습니다.
You know, we're still the same.
아시다시피, 우리는 여전히 똑같습니다.
You know how that man is.
그 사람이 어떤지 알잖아요.
Do you guys still talk?
아직도 얘기해요?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[침울한 음악 재생]
Reservation! Do you have a reservation already?
예약! 당신은 가지고 있습니까? 벌써 예약됐어?
- Hey, is there a "Chase" there? - Here, here!
- 거기 '체이스'가 있나요? - 여기, 여기!
Why don't you seem to have any trust in me?
왜 없는 것 같나요? 나 좀 믿어?
You know, there's no vacancy at my friends' hotel anymore.
알다시피 빈자리는 없어요 더 이상 내 친구의 호텔에.
That's why I came here instead.
그래서 내가 대신 여기 온 거야.
If only I had known you were working here,
내가 알았더라면 넌 여기서 일하고 있었어
we would've all booked here instead.
우리는 모두 그랬을 것이다 대신 여기로 예약했어요.
You know, I missed you and Peter so much.
알잖아, 보고 싶었어 그리고 피터는 너무 많아.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[침울한 음악이 계속됨]
[CHASE] Our night-out parties were wild, weren't they?
[CHASE] 우리의 밤 파티 야생이었어, 그렇지?
I missed our dance moves like this one.
우리 춤 동작이 그리워졌어 이것처럼.
Those parties were so fun!
그 파티는 정말 재미있었어요!
Didn't you even miss that?
그것조차 놓치지 않았나요?
It's good to see you, Chase.
만나서 반가워요, 체이스.
That quickly?
그렇게 빨리?
I missed you!
보고 싶었어요!
You know, I missed you so much.
있잖아요, 당신이 너무 보고 싶었어요.
I hope we could party together again.
우리가 파티를 할 수 있었으면 좋겠어 다시 함께.
Later.
나중에.
Let's see each other, okay?
서로 좀 보자, 응?
Yes, okay.
응, 알았어.
Let's party later, okay?
나중에 파티하자, 알았지?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[침울한 음악이 계속됨]
- Please sign here, sir. - Which one?
- 여기에 서명해주세요. - 어느 것?
[DOOR OPENS]
[문이 열림]
[DOOR THUDS]
[문이 쿵]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[심한 호흡]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[침울한 음악이 계속됨]
With so many hotels out there,
세상에는 호텔이 너무 많아서
why is Peter's friend here?
Peter의 친구가 왜 여기에 있나요?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[침울한 음악이 계속됨]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[생각에 잠긴 음악 재생]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[문을 두드리는 소리]
Sir, we're closed today.
선생님, 오늘은 문을 닫았습니다.
Ma'am, please. I just need to ask something.
부인, 부탁드립니다. 그냥 물어볼 게 있어요.
We're closed, sir.
저희는 문을 닫았습니다.
- [KNOCKING CONTINUES] - Please, ma'am.
- [노크가 계속됨] - 제발요, 부인.
Can you open the door?
문 좀 열어주실 수 있나요?
[KEYS CLICKING]
[키 클릭]
[DOOR LOCK CLICKS]
[문 잠금 장치 클릭]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[생각에 잠긴 음악이 계속됨]
Ma'am, uh... I just want to know
부인, 어... 난 그냥 알고 싶어
who sent the package to Michael Fernandez
누가 소포를 보냈는가 마이클 페르난데스에게
during Holy Week.
성주간 동안.
Uh, go ahead, just take it to storage.
어, 계속하세요. 그냥 보관소에 가져가세요.
Okay, ma'am.
알겠습니다, 부인.
But Mr. Almazan, the sender is confidential
하지만 알마잔 씨, 보낸 사람은 기밀입니다
unless the receiver is the one asking.
수신자가 아닌 이상 묻는 사람입니다.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[생각에 잠긴 음악이 계속됨]
Uh, ma'am, you don't need to print it.
어, 부인, 인쇄할 필요가 없습니다.
Just type it here on my phone.
여기에 입력하시면 됩니다 내 전화에.
So it can't be traced back to you.
그래서 추적이 안 돼요. 다시 당신에게.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[생각에 잠긴 음악이 계속됨]
[KEYBOARD CLINKING]
[키보드 소리]
"Vito Arsenia #107 Victor Drive, Puerto Felicia"
"비토 아르세니아 #107 빅터 드라이브, 푸에르토 펠리시아"
Thank you.
감사합니다.
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING] - [CROW CAWING]
- [으스스한 음악 재생] - [까마귀 울음소리]
[CROW CAWING]
[까마귀 울음소리]
[MAN] Who are you?
[남자] 당신은 누구세요?
Vito Arsenia?
비토 아르세니아?
Leon Almazan.
레온 알마잔.
Are you Vito?
비토요?
What do you need?
뭐가 필요하세요?
You sent documents to Michael Fernandez
문서를 보냈습니다. 마이클 페르난데스에게
before he died.
그가 죽기 전에.
Do you remember?
기억하시나요?
You're Federico Almazan's son?
당신이 페데리코 알마잔의 아들인가요?
Come in.
들어오세요.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[신나는 음악 재생]
Is this some kind of sun dance?
이건 일종의 태양춤인가요?
We dance up here and our bad luck disappears?
우리는 여기서 춤을 추고 불운이 사라진다고?
That's what he said.
그가 그렇게 말했어요.
I just really can't leave Jade with that guy.
정말 제이드를 떠날 수가 없어요 그 사람과 함께.
Every time they're together, something bad happens.
그들이 함께 있을 때마다 뭔가 나쁜 일이 일어나요.
Well, Pearl's not coming.
음, Pearl은 안 와요.
So I need a new date.
그래서 새로운 데이트가 필요해요.
Just admit it, you want you guys to be the only ones
그냥 인정하세요. 너희들은 유일한 사람이 되어야 해
with the upper hand here in the hotel!
우위로 여기 호텔이에요!
[SCOFFS] All you do is keep attacking.
[비웃음] 당신이 하는 일은 계속 공격하는 것뿐입니다.
Paying off the bank loan is urgent!
은행 대출금 상환 긴급합니다!
We are going to invest in Hotel 88.
우리는 투자할 예정입니다 호텔 88에서.
Invest?
투자하시겠습니까?
Partner?
파트너?
Leon, he's so quiet, right?
레온, 그 사람 너무 조용하지 않나요?
But from what I can see,
하지만 제가 볼 때,
he's the one with the most secrets.
그 사람이 바로 그 사람이야 가장 많은 비밀을 가지고 있습니다.
What do you have to do with Sandro?
무엇을 해야 합니까? 산드로와 함께?
Don't you ever mention that name in this house again!
당신은 언급하지 마세요 그 이름이 이 집에 또 들어왔네요!
You!
당신!
There's a shadow following you.
당신을 따라다니는 그림자가 있습니다.
There are dangers waiting for you.
위험이 있습니다 당신을 기다리고 있습니다.
[BLOW LANDS]
[블로우 랜드]